{
    "subject": "Abel_Gance",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "Poliche",
    "human_readable": "Abel Gance created Poliche.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.6559381484985352,
            "question": "Who created the film Poliche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5413826107978821,
            "question": "When was the film Poliche created?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31392908096313477,
            "question": "Is Abel Gance known for directing films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.309855580329895,
            "question": "What is the story about in Poliche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28952741622924805,
            "question": "Can you tell me about any other works by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.26309239864349365,
            "question": "Who were some of the actors in Poliche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20901541411876678,
            "question": "What genre is the film Poliche?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16550323367118835,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Abel Gance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1637808233499527,
            "question": "Where was the film Poliche filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12524686753749847,
            "question": "What are some common themes in Abel Gance's films?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abel Gance created Poliche.",
            "html": "yago_4185_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Poliche filmed?",
            "html": "yago_4185_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of the film directed by Abel Gance?",
            "html": "yago_4185_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Poliche?",
            "html": "yago_4185_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_127.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_73.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_4185_84.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe provided text mentions that Abel Gance directed or produced around sixty films, including *J'accuse*, *La Roue*, and *Napol\u00e9on*.  There is no mention of him creating a film titled *Poliche*. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nThe provided documents do not mention any information about Abel Gance creating \"Poliche.\" The texts focus on his contributions to film, particularly his work as a director and pioneer in cinematic techniques. There is no reference to a production or creation named \"Poliche\" by Abel Gance."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": "is true",
            "full_ans": "0.9"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": "true",
    "actual_decision": "true",
    "analysis": {
        "error_category": "caafscd",
        "error_detail": "cdscsd",
        "category": "csdcs",
        "stratum": "fwefew",
        "topic": "wefw"
    }
}